The United States was Israel before Israel. The Constitution is literally just a document to
present outwardly what the United States is supposed to be received as, but not what they're
going to live by. The same way that Israel is called the only democracy in the Middle East
and the most moral army ever. It's all just a front. It's all just sleight of hand.
And Black people and Palestinians are incredibly similar because Black peoples have spent so much
time, basically being like, okay, US, you said you were this, so stand by it and really demanding
that and doing so in very peaceful fashion for the most part. Palestinians, same thing. They were
like, okay, Jews, you came in here and we was cool, but now you flipped the script on us and you want
some other thing. And because they are a people of faith, they in many ways have stuck with that
while also being like, okay, but y'all doing too much. So similarities I think are always very
important, especially to expanding our critical thinking skills doing comparative analysis
also helps us understand like methodology that works and hasn't worked. And one thing I will say
is that Black folks, we have allowed ourselves to be colonized in ways that Palestinians have not,
by and large. And that is, I believe, largely because we did not stay connected to the land in the way
that Palestinians have. It's all magic, i.e. manipulation. Magic is the manipulation of energy.
Dark magic is manipulating that energy for the effort of toxicity, destruction, etc.
They're manipulating your energy. And so they literally created a reality in words,
but not an action. And the spell has people so enraptured that they are continuously putting
their energy into trying to make the words true instead of trying to stop the actions.
So anywho, just wanted to say that.